

RIZKI PRATAMA

081388006534 | rizki191220@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/rizk1pratama

South Jakarta, Kamp Pluis Street

I am a 6th-semester informatics engineering student at Mercubuana University. I am also a member of the UMB informatics engineering student association as the head of the public relations division. my current expertise and interest in web development. I hope that the knowledge and experience I gained during college and in organizations can help me work optimally

Work Experiences

Education Assessment Center, Ministry of Education and Culture Republic of Indonesia - Central Jakarta

Aug 2018 - May 2019

Assistant Support

Implementation and preparation of technical policies for the development of educational assessment and learning development. Coordinate and facilitate the implementation of the development of education and learning assessments.

- Phase-I online question writing study activity (English and math group)
- Phase-II online question writing activity (language and religious groups)

Ministry of Agrarian Affaris and Spatial Planning/National Land Agency of Republic Indonesia - South Jakarta

Mar 2017 - May 2017

Administration Staff (Practical field)

Responsible for documents to be able to carry out government affairs in the field of agrarian/land and spatial planning to assist the President in running the government of the country.

· Received "Good" predicate for administrative staff as participants in fieldwork practice

MarkPlus, Inc - South Jakarta

Mar 2022 -

Web Developer Intern

Responsible for assisting in making UI/UX design using Figma, changing the frontend (CSS, Bootstrap, etc), redeveloping the website using another framework (Codelgniter 4 / Laravel), and helping configure the server

Education Level

Mercubuana University - Meruya, West Jakarta

Aug 2019 - Aug 2023 (Expected)

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.79/4.00

- (Project Task) Successfully made Anis-Laundry, a web-based laundry ordering application with a shuttle system
- (Project Task) Successfully made KiCoffe, a web-based food, and beverage ordering application.
- (Project Task) Succeeded in making a diabetic patient detection system

Barunawati Vocational High School - West Jakarta

Aug 2015 - Aug 2018

High School Diploma in Multimedia

Received "Good" predicate on multimedia skill competency exam

Organisational Experience

HiMTI UMB - Mercubuana University, West Jakarta head of public relations

Dec 2021 - Present

- Become a liaison between HiMTI and the campus internal and external public
- Fostering a harmonious relationship between the organization and the campus internal and external public

Skills, Achievements & Others

- Hard Skills (2019): Programming Language C++, Python, Java, HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, SQL, Framework (CI, Laravel, VueJs)
- Soft Skills: Good leadership, Ability to work under pressure, Ability to work in a team, good problem solver.
- Interest (2018): Web Developer Frontend Developer, Backend Developer, Fullstack Developer
- Achievements (2019): Machine Learning with Python. Data Science Methodology. Python 101 for Data Science. Database Programming with PL/SQL. Certified Secure Computer User (CSCU) v2 (Complete Series).
- **Projects** (2022): KiCoffe, a web-based food, and beverage ordering application.
- Projects (2021): Anis-Laundry, a web-based laundry ordering application with a shuttle system